Guide to the Ship Scalers, Dry Dock, and Boat Yard Workers Union, Local 541 (Seattle, Washington) Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Ship Scalers, Dry Dock, and Boat Yard Workers Union, Local 541 (Seattle, Washington) Records, 1939-1991; 4571-001; 16 cubic feet 16 boxes
  - Series VII: Member Files, 1944-1986 (Box-folder 12/1-12/44; 16/9; 12/45-14/246)
    - Subseries A: Non-Alphabetized or Multi-Member Files, 1951-1986 (Box-folder 12/1-12/44; 16/9)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 12/6)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1981 (Box-folder 12/7)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1982 (Box-folder 12/8)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 12/9)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1982 (Box-folder 12/10)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1982 (Box-folder 12/11)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1984 (Box-folder 12/12)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1964-1982 (Box-folder 12/13)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1982 (Box-folder 12/14)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1982 (Box-folder 12/15)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1980 (Box-folder 12/16)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1982 (Box-folder 12/17)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 12/18)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 12/19)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 12/20)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1977-1984 (Box-folder 12/21)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 12/22)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 12/23)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1980 (Box-folder 12/24)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 12/25)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1981 (Box-folder 12/26)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 12/27)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 12/28)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 12/29)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 12/30)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1984 (Box-folder 12/31)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 12/32)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 12/33)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1982 (Box-folder 12/34)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1982 (Box-folder 12/35)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1961-1982 (Box-folder 12/36)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1981 (Box-folder 12/37)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 12/38)
      - Member Files: Not Arranged Alphabetically, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 12/39)
      - Grievances (1 of 2), 1966-1980 (Box-folder 12/40)
      - Grievances (2 of 2), 1966-1980 (Box-folder 12/41)
      - Correspondence Regarding Members: State of Washington Department of Social and Health Services, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 12/42)
      - Grievances, Motions, Correspondence, Press, History, Strikes, Tensions with International, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 12/43)
      - Grievances, Legal Documents, Press, Negotiations, Minutes, 1951-1981 (Box-folder 12/44)
      - Member Lists, Political Correspondence, and Employment Security Hearing Documents, 1958-1973 (Box-folder 16/9)
    - Subseries B: Member Files: A-Z, 1944-1986 (Box-folder 12/45-14/220)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1982-1982 (Box-folder 12/45)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1984-1984 (Box-folder 12/46)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 12/47)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 12/48)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 12/49)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 12/50)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 12/51)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1984-1984 (Box-folder 12/52)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1986-1986 (Box-folder 12/53)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 12/54)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 12/55)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1982 (Box-folder 12/56)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 12/57)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1982 (Box-folder 12/58)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1984 (Box-folder 12/59)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1982 (Box-folder 12/60)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 12/61)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1983 (Box-folder 12/62)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1982 (Box-folder 12/63)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 12/64)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1982 (Box-folder 12/65)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 12/66)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1982 (Box-folder 12/67)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 12/68)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1970 (Box-folder 12/69)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1981 (Box-folder 12/70)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 12/71)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 12/72)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1981 (Box-folder 12/73)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 12/74)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with A, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 12/74)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1983 (Box-folder 12/75)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 12/76)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 12/77)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 12/78)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1983 (Box-folder 12/79)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 12/80)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 12/81)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1984-1984 (Box-folder 12/82)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1982 (Box-folder 12/83)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1981 (Box-folder 12/84)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1946-1986 (Box-folder 12/85)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1983 (Box-folder 12/86)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1982 (Box-folder 12/87)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 12/88)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 12/89)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 12/90)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 12/91)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 12/92)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1982 (Box-folder 12/93)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1984 (Box-folder 12/94)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 12/95)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1986 (Box-folder 12/96)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 12/97)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 12/98)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1983 (Box-folder 12/99)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1983 (Box-folder 12/100)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 12/101)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 12/102)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 12/103)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1982 (Box-folder 12/104)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1985 (Box-folder 12/105)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 12/106)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1980 (Box-folder 12/107)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1980-1980 (Box-folder 12/108)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 12/109)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1974-1986 (Box-folder 12/110)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 12/111)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 12/112)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 12/113)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1981 (Box-folder 12/114)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1981 (Box-folder 12/115)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1972-1982 (Box-folder 12/116)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 12/117)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1982-1982 (Box-folder 12/118)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 12/119)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 12/120)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1980-1980 (Box-folder 12/121)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 12/122)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1982 (Box-folder 12/123)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 12/124)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1982 (Box-folder 12/125)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1981 (Box-folder 12/126)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 12/127)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1983 (Box-folder 12/128)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with B, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 12/129)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 12/130)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 12/131)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 12/132)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1982-1982 (Box-folder 12/133)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1980-1980 (Box-folder 12/134)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 12/135)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1983 (Box-folder 12/136)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1983 (Box-folder 12/137)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1981 (Box-folder 12/138)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 12/139)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 12/140)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 12/141)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1982-1982 (Box-folder 12/142)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 12/143)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1980-1980 (Box-folder 12/144)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 12/145)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 12/146)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1982 (Box-folder 12/147)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1981 (Box-folder 12/148)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 12/149)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 12/150)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1982 (Box-folder 12/151)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1982 (Box-folder 12/152)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1980-1980 (Box-folder 12/153)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 12/154)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1982 (Box-folder 12/155)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1982 (Box-folder 12/156)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1980 (Box-folder 12/157)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1985 (Box-folder 12/158)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1982 (Box-folder 12/159)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1984 (Box-folder 12/160)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1980 (Box-folder 12/161)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1982 (Box-folder 12/162)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1981 (Box-folder 12/163)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 12/164)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1981 (Box-folder 12/165)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 12/166)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1983 (Box-folder 12/167)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with C, 1983 (Box-folder 12/168)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with D, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 12/169)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with D, 1982 (Box-folder 12/170)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with D, 1982 (Box-folder 12/171)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with D, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 12/172)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with D, 1981 (Box-folder 12/173)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with D, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 12/174)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with D, 1984 (Box-folder 12/175)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with D, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 12/176)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with D, 1980 (Box-folder 12/177)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with D, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 12/178)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with D, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 12/179)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with D, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 12/180)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with D, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 12/181)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with D, 1982 (Box-folder 12/182)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with D, 1984 (Box-folder 12/183)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with D, 1975 (Box-folder 12/184)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with D, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 12/185)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with D, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 12/186)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with D, 1984 (Box-folder 12/187)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with E, 1984 (Box-folder 13/1)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with E, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 13/2)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with E, 1981 (Box-folder 13/3)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with E, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 13/4)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with E, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 13/5)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with E, 1980 (Box-folder 13/6)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with E, 1983 (Box-folder 13/7)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with E, 1981 (Box-folder 13/8)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with E, 1982 (Box-folder 13/9)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with E, 1982 (Box-folder 13/10)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with E, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 13/11)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with E, 1981 (Box-folder 13/12)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with F, 1983 (Box-folder 13/13)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with F, 1981 (Box-folder 13/14)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with F, 1984 (Box-folder 13/15)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with F, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 13/16)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with F, 1982 (Box-folder 13/17)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with F, 1984 (Box-folder 13/18)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with F, 1981 (Box-folder 13/19)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with F, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 13/20)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with F, 1984 (Box-folder 13/21)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with F, 1986 (Box-folder 13/22)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with F, 1982 (Box-folder 13/23)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 13/24)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1981 (Box-folder 13/25)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 13/26)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 13/27)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 13/28)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1981 (Box-folder 13/29)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1983 (Box-folder 13/30)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1981 (Box-folder 13/31)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1982 (Box-folder 13/32)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1982 (Box-folder 13/33)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1983 (Box-folder 13/34)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1978-1986 (Box-folder 13/35)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 13/36)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1984 (Box-folder 13/37)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1977-1984 (Box-folder 13/38)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 13/39)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 13/40)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1983 (Box-folder 13/41)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 13/42)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1983 (Box-folder 13/43)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 13/44)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1982 (Box-folder 13/45)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 13/46)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1984 (Box-folder 13/47)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1983 (Box-folder 13/48)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1981 (Box-folder 13/49)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1979 (Box-folder 13/50)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1979 (Box-folder 13/51)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1980 (Box-folder 13/52)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 13/53)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1982 (Box-folder 13/54)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 13/55)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1982 (Box-folder 13/56)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 13/57)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1979 (Box-folder 13/58)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with G, 1981 (Box-folder 13/59)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1982 (Box-folder 13/60)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1981 (Box-folder 13/61)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1980 (Box-folder 13/62)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1980 (Box-folder 13/63)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1983 (Box-folder 13/64)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1982 (Box-folder 13/65)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1983 (Box-folder 13/66)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1980 (Box-folder 13/67)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1983 (Box-folder 13/68)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 13/69)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 13/70)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 13/71)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 13/72)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1983 (Box-folder 13/73)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 13/74)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 13/75)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1985 (Box-folder 13/76)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 13/77)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 13/78)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1965-1984 (Box-folder 13/79)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1985 (Box-folder 13/80)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 13/81)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1982 (Box-folder 13/82)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 13/83)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1984 (Box-folder 13/84)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1970-1986 (Box-folder 13/85)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 13/86)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 13/87)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1985 (Box-folder 13/88)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 13/89)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1978 (Box-folder 13/90)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 13/91)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 13/92)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 13/93)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 13/94)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1980 (Box-folder 13/95)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1980 (Box-folder 13/96)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 13/97)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 13/98)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1981 (Box-folder 13/99)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1985 (Box-folder 13/100)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 13/101)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1983 (Box-folder 13/102)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1984 (Box-folder 13/103)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 13/104)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1982 (Box-folder 13/105)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 13/106)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1982 (Box-folder 13/107)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 13/108)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1972-1980 (Box-folder 13/109)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 13/110)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with H, 1982 (Box-folder 13/111)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with I, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 13/112)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with I, 1980 (Box-folder 13/113)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with I, 1981 (Box-folder 13/114)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with I, 1981 (Box-folder 13/115)